[
  {
    "title": "True/False",
    "questions":[
      {
        "question": "The sky is blue?",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [true, false]
      },
      {
        "question": "Munich is the capital of Germany?",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [true, false]
      },
      {
        "question": "Lighting never strikes the same place twice?",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [true, false]
      },
      {
        "question": "Otters have the thickest fur of any mammal?",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [true, false]
      },
      {
        "question": "Sea otters have a pouch to store their favorite rock?",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [true, false]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Animal Multiple Choice",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What type of animal is a seahorse?",
        "options": ["Crustacean", "Arachnid", "Fish", "Shell"],
        "answer": "crustacean"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following dogs is the smallest?",
        "options": ["Dachshund", "Poodle", "Pomeranian", "Chihuahua"],
        "answer": "chihuahua"
      },
      {
        "question": "What existing bird has the largest wingspan?",
        "options": ["Stork", "Swan", "Condor", "Albatross"],
        "answer": "albatross"
      },
      {
        "question": "What pets do more families own?",
        "options": ["Birds", "Cats", "Dogs", "Horses"],
        "answer": "dogs"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following animals sleep standing up?",
        "options": ["Gorillas", "Flamingos", "Camels", "Ravens"],
        "answer": "flamingos"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Harry Potter Multiple Choice",
    "questions":[
      {
        "question" : "Which is not a magical means of transportation?",
        "options" : ["Portkey", "Floo Powder", "Knight Bus", "Gambol and Japes"],
        "answer" : "gambol and japes"
      },
      {
        "question" : "Which of the following dragons was NOT used in the Triwizard Tournament in 1994?",
        "options": ["Swedish Short-Snout", "Norwegian Ridgeback", "Common Welsh Green", "Chinese Fireball", "Hungarian Horntail"],
        "answer" : "norwegian ridgeback"
      },
      {
        "question" : "Which of the Marauders was not an animagus?",
        "options": ["Sirius Black", "Remus Lupin", "James Potter", "Peter Pettigrew"],
        "answer" : "remus lupin"
      },
      {
        "question" : "Newt Scamander's mother bred what magical creature?",
        "options": ["Hippogriffs", "Winged Horses", "Unicorns", "Nifflers"],
        "answer" : "hippogriffs"
      },
      {
        "question" : "Which one is not a house elf featured in the books?",
        "options": ["Dobby", "Winky", "Hooky", "Kreacher", "Hokey"],
        "answer" : "hooky"
      }
    ]

  }
]
